iona.ie 2002-12-18

# Welcome to IONA - About US

#### IONA Privacy Policy

IONA Technologies has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for [www.iona.com](http://www.iona.com/) and other Internet web sites owned by IONA Technologies. 

**Information Collected**

In general, you can visit the IONA website without providing personal information, but there are times when we will request personal information, such as contact and credit card information. In some situations, you may be required to provide personal information in order to participate in our site's activities and offerings. Information is typically requested when you wish to download evaluation products, enter contests, subscribe to online services, participate in one of our online communities or when you are ordering products or services on our site. 

We may also collect information when you visit our web site through the use of "cookie" technology, including web beacons and action tags. The information gathered may include your password and IP address, the type of browser and operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider and site visitation statistics. 

IONA is a global company, with offices and operations throughout the world. When you submit personal information to IONA through its web site, you agree that your information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which IONA and its affiliates are located. 

**How We Use the Information**

We collect and use your information in order to give you better service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services and to make our website more useful to you. The contact information we collect is used to deliver orders, information about our Company and partners and promotional material to you. It is also used to contact you when necessary. Credit card or other financial information is used to facilitate purchases and to pay for products and services you order through our site. Information collected through the use of cookies is used to evaluate and improve our website and to help diagnose problems with our server. Cookies also help us to deliver content specific to your interests and allow us to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

IONA will only disclose your personal information without notice when it believes disclosure to be required by law or regulation, or necessary to protect or defend the rights or property of IONA, the safety of the public or the users of its site. 

**Public Forums**   
Our site makes forums, message boards and/or newsgroups available to its users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public information. IONA is not responsible for the content or protection of any information disclosed in these areas. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
When you provide us with your contact information, you may opt-out of receiving communications from us. You may also be removed from receiving email information about IONA at any time by sending an email with your name and email address to [remove@iona.com](mailto:remove@iona.com). 

**Links to Other Sites**   
IONA's web sites may contain links to other sites whose privacy and information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices. IONA is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other sites. 

**Security**   
We use physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard the information we collect from you online. We urge you to take precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often and make sure you use a secure browser. 

**Correcting Information/ Contacting the Web Site**   
If you wish to correct any information you have provided to us or if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our web site, you can contact the [webmaster @iona.com](mailto:webmaster%20@iona.com). 

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice. Last edited December 27, 2001
